<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Scraly tech blog</title>
    <link>https://scraly.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Scraly tech blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;http://scraly.com&#34;&gt;Aurélie Vache&lt;/a&gt; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 16:09:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scraly.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Multiple Environments With Terraform Workspaces</title>
      <link>https://scraly.github.io/posts/manage-multiple-environments-with-terraform-workspaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 16:09:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scraly.github.io/posts/manage-multiple-environments-with-terraform-workspaces/</guid>
      <description>The beginning When you want to manage (create, modify and remove) your infrastructure, getting started with Terraform is easy. Just create files ending with .tf containing the description of the resources you want to have.
For example, if we want to create a small infrastructure in AWS cloud provider:
 a S3 bucket (for terraform) a S3 bucket (for our website) a S3 bucket (for website logs) a CloudFront distribution (without SSl for this example)  We just need to create some .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Struggle With Librdkafka</title>
      <link>https://scraly.github.io/posts/struggle-with-librdkafka/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 07:36:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scraly.github.io/posts/struggle-with-librdkafka/</guid>
      <description>The beginning For an event driven microservice project in golang that was supposed to communicate with the Kafka message broker, among other things, I decided to use the confluent kafka go client. To connect to a Kafka and create a producer and / or a consumer, the grip is super fast. Perfect. Ah &amp;hellip; but you have to use a librdkafka library. Whats is that?
 librdkafka is the Apache Kafka C/C++ library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When I grow up I would like ...</title>
      <link>https://scraly.github.io/posts/wish-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:31:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scraly.github.io/posts/wish-list/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago, if I had been asked what I would have liked to do when I grew up, I think I would never have thought of making the list that you will see below.
I have been a developer for more than 12 years, doing Front, back, devops, big data and a period as lead developer. I am passionate about my work and I like to share with others. This thirst for sharing and mutual help made me immerse myself in associative work and communities of developers and meetups.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>